kikki-k.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Thanks for being a kikki.K lover and shopping with us. Your privacy is important to us, so we (kikki.K Pty Ltd) acknowledge and are committed to protecting your privacy, as well as that of other third parties who provide personal information to us. The following Privacy Policy outlines the information we collect about you, how we use the information and the choices you have to review or restrict this. 

**1\. Scope of Our Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy explains how we gather information about you and how we may store, maintain and use that information.

Our Privacy Policy includes disclosure of the matters set out in the Australian Privacy Principles.

**  
2\. Personal information we collect**

When used in this policy, “personal information” has the meaning given to that term in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). Personal information generally includes any information that can be used to personally identify you.

**  
3\. When do we collect your personal information?**

At times, we are required to collect personal information in the normal course of providing services for our customers. The services may include:

• Making customer purchases  
• Registering for a kikki.K Workshop  
• Accepting customer orders  
• Processing credit card payments  
• Arranging product holds  
• Accepting gift voucher payments  
• During conversations with our team members;  
• When you communicate with us directly (by email, telephone, direct mail or any other means);   
• When you interact with us by using devices within our stores; or  
• If you are a candidate for employment, when you complete forms in relation to the recruitment and selection process, for the purpose of assessment.

We may also collect personal information about you from the following third parties:

• If you are a candidate for employment, we may collect information about you from your nominated referees, where you have authorised us to do so.

Normally we collect information from you directly, unless it is unreasonable or impracticable to do so.

**  
4\. What personal information we may collect?**

We may collect the following types of personal information from you:

• Your name and contact details such as your residential or business address, email address and telephone number;  
• Your gender, age and date of birth and occupation;  
• Your company name (if applicable);  
• Your signature;  
• Proof of identity, such as your driver’s licence or passport number;  
• A photograph or video surveillance recording of you if you are physically present in our stores;   
• If you are a candidate for employment, we may collect other information as further set out in our application forms or during the recruitment process. This may include information relating to your employment history, working eligibility rights, suitability for the role you are applying for, and your referee details;  
• Other information you may supply to us.

**  
5\. Other information**

We may also collect information from you that is not personal information because it does not identify you personally. This information is normally retained with your personal information and may include:

• Your shopping preferences and a list of products and services you have purchased from kikki.K. This may include your shopping history, items, colours, or other attributes of products and services we have provided to you or may provide to you in the future;   
• Information we require to deliver, service or fulfil warranty obligations for products or services;  
• Your marketing preferences, including the type of marketing materials you wish to receive and the method of delivery (email, SMS, direct mail, or other);  
• Information you provide to us via application forms, or directly to team members within our stores in relation to our products and services.

**  
6\. Purpose of collection of your personal information**

We collect your personal information so that we can carry out the following actions :  
• To provide you with products and services that you have requested from us;  
• To provide you with relevant consumer information and notify you of products and special offers that may be of interest to you  
• To communicate with you, including about products and services, special offers, and events which might interest you;  
• To answer your questions and provide you with information or advice;  
• To create orders, transaction records, agreements for the sale of products or services, accounts, tax invoices or receipts;   
• Provide your personal information to third parties that assist us in providing products and services you have requested, such as delivery service providers;  
• Carry out administration, marketing, planning, fraud and loss prevention activities, procurement, product and service development, quality control and research to improve the way kikki.K and its related bodies corporate and service providers provide products and services to you;  
• To consider and respond to complaints made by you;  
• To comply with laws or regulations or to comply with any directions given by regulators or authorities;  
• If you are a candidate for employment, to assess your suitability for a position at kikki.K.

**  
7\. If we are unable to collect your personal information**

If we are unable to collect your personal information, some or all of the following may occur:

• We may be unable to provide products or services to you, to the requested standard or at all;  
• We may be unable to communicate with you to provide information about products and services that you have purchased from us, or may intend to purchase in the future;  
• We may be unable to tailor the content of our marketing communications to suit your preferences;  
• Your experience when interacting with us may be delayed or not as efficient as you may expect;  
• If you are a candidate for employment, we may not be able to process your application for a position at kikki.K.

**8\. Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is saved to, and, during subsequent visits, retrieved from your computer or mobile device. kikki.K uses cookies to enhance and simplify your visit. We do not use cookies to store personal information, or to disclose information to third parties. We use temporary (session cookies) to check whether you are logged in or if you put an item in your shopping bag. You can easily erase cookies from your computer or mobile device using your browser. For instructions on how to handle and delete cookies please look under "Help" in your browser. You can choose to disable cookies, or to receive a notification each time a new cookie is sent to your computer or mobile device. Please note that if you choose to disable cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of all our features.

_Third-party cookies_   
We use third-party cookies to collect statistics in aggregate form in analysis tools such as Google Analytics. The cookies used are both permanent and temporary cookies (session cookies). The permanent cookies are stored on your computer or mobile device for no longer than 24 months.  
We also use third-party cookies for remarketing through our website or other social media channels. Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies. Information about how you can opt out of Google's use of cookies can be found by visiting [Google's Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated).

**  
9\. How we hold your personal information**

We may hold your personal information in either electronic or hard copy form.

If you provide information to us electronically we retain this information in our computer systems and databases. This includes computer software programs, internet servers and hosted internet solutions provided by third parties.

If you provide information to us in hard copy (paper), this information is destroyed once it has been transferred to our electronic files.

**  
10\. Security of your personal information**

We understand the importance of your personal information and have appropriate procedures in place to safeguard and secure the information we collect to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information.

**  
11\. Disclosure of your personal information**

Your personal information may be disclosed to any of the following:

• our employees, contractors or service providers, to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfil our obligations to you. This may include internet service providers, IT systems administrators, mailing houses, couriers, payment processors, and data entry service providers;  
• our business advisors, including lawyers, accountants or other professional service providers, to the extent reasonably required;  
• suppliers and other third parties with whom we have commercial relationships, for business, marketing and related purposes;   
• if required by law, to any person authorised by such law. This may include the police service, ambulance service, or government departments or regulators within Australia in connection with law enforcement activities.

Where applicable information is shared with a third party, these third parties are obliged to observe the confidential nature of such information and are prohibited from using any or all of this information other than for the purpose for which it was provided.

Some of our associated companies with whom we share personal information may be located overseas. These associated companies will often be subject to privacy and confidentiality obligations dictated by laws in their own jurisdictions. Nevertheless, we will take such steps as are reasonable in the circumstances to ensure that the overseas recipient does not breach relevant privacy law or principles.  
Your personal information will not be shared, sold, rented or disclosed other than as described in this Privacy Policy.

**  
12\. Direct Marketing Communications**

We may send you direct marketing communications and information about products and services offered by us via email, SMS or regular mail.

If you have indicated a preference for a method of communication, we will endeavor to use that method wherever practical to do so.

You may opt out of receiving marketing communications at any time by responding via the channel in which you received the marketing communication or by contacting us via the details provided in section 13.

You can unsubscribe from emails by clicking the unsubscribe link on the footer of the email communication you have received.

We do not provide your personal information to any other organisations for the purposes of direct marketing.

**  
13\. How you may access your personal information**

You may access your personal information held by kikki.K by making a request to us.

Email: info@kikki-k.com   
Phone: 03 9645 6346  
Mail: kikki.K, Suite 203, Level 2, 120 Bay St, Port Melbourne VIC 3207 AUSTRALIA

Normally we will provide a record of your personal information to you via your preferred contact method (phone, email or mail) and we will not charge a fee.

If your request is unlawful or may interfere with the privacy of others we may reasonably refuse to provide access to your personal information.

**  
14\. Correction of your personal information**

If you would like us to update or amend your personal information, please contact us and we will make the requested amendments.

We may ask you to verify your identity to ensure that personal information we hold is not improperly accessed.

**  
15\. Candidates and employees**

If you are a candidate for employment, you may alternatively contact (email) in relation to this Privacy Policy or to access, update or amend your personal information.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to current and former employees of kikki.K. If you are a current or former employee and have a query about your personal information, please contact the HR department.

**  
16\. Privacy Complaints**

If you believe that we have breached your privacy rights in any way or you would like to discuss any issues about our privacy policy please contact our Privacy Officer (contact details below).

All such enquiries or complaints will be taken seriously and handled with impartiality and discretion.

If you wish to submit a complaint, please provide us with all relevant details such as the date and time of the incident or communication, the circumstances surrounding the event and your concerns about what was said or done. You will also receive an acknowledgment from us within 7 days confirming receipt of your complaint.

Once you have submitted your complaint we will assess it to determine whether or not you have complained about a privacy issue which is covered by the relevant privacy laws. If you have complained about something which is not appropriately dealt with under privacy law, we will write to you and explain why our Privacy Officer is unable to address your complaint.

If you have complained about something which the relevant privacy laws cover, we will thoroughly investigate all aspects of your complaint including ascertaining the relevant facts and what your expectations are for any resolution. During our investigation we may need to seek further information from you as to the nature of or factual circumstances surrounding your complaint.

We will endeavor to respond to you, using your preferred contact method if you have indicated one, at all times promptly and to offer a practical solution which is consistent with our legal obligations.

**  
17\. Australia Post eParcel tracking emails**

By shopping with kikki.K, Australian and New Zealand customers agree to receive emails from Australia Post eParcel system. You will receive a series of emails from Australia Post which provides updates on the progress of your order delivery. You can unsubscribe from these emails at any time via the link in the email or through managing your MyPost account. For more information about Australia Post's Privacy Policy, please see the Australia Post website [here](http://auspost.com.au/privacy.html?ilink=track-em0b-edm-privacy-policy).

If you have any concerns about these emails, please contact our Customer Experience Team at [info@kikki-k.com](mailto:info@kikki-k.com) or call +61 3 9645 6346.

**18\. Contacting us**

If you would like to contact us in relation to this Privacy Policy, data protection or your personal information please contact us at:

Email: info@kikki-k.com  
Mail: The Privacy Officer  
kikki.K Pty Ltd  
PO Box 107  
Albert Park VIC 3206

This privacy policy is current at the date below. We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Please contact us using the contact information above if you would like an updated version of our Privacy Policy.

Last update of this policy: 30 June 2014

If you have any questions, please call us on +61 3 9645 6346 or email [info@kikki-k.com](mailto:info@kikki-k.com).
